# SAUL RAFAEL TEJEDA MILIAN

#### IT ENGINEER

- **\ +52 33 13 11 70 80**
- @ linkedin.com/in/saultejeda
- Guadalajara

- @ saultejm@gmail.com
- github.com/saulTejeda117



# **ABOUT**

Engineer graduated from the University of Guadalajara in the field of computer engineering with experience in web application development, process automation, machine learning, and data analysis with Python. Passionate about problem-solving and deeply committed to the quality

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Information Systems Intern

#### SUDISA Súper Diesel S.A.

iii 09/2022 - Present ♀ Jalisco

Professional Development Program in this company dedicated to the manufacturing of axles for heavy-duty vehicles, where I performed technical support tasks on computer equipment, as well as developed, updated, and documented various systems in Python.

- IT Support
- Python Development
- Process Documentation
- Networking

### Research Intern

#### **UNAM Juriquilla**

**m** 06/2022 - 08/2022 Querétaro

Research project focused on the development of a supervised machine learning application aimed at detecting diabetic macular edema through the classification and analysis of optical coherence tomography images.

- Python Development
- Data Visualization
- Data Analysis
- Machine Learning

## IT Support

#### Vanquardia Lux

**=** 2019 - 06/2022 Jalisco

Freelance work in maintenance and repair of computer equipment, printers, electronic devices, etc.

- . IT Support
- Networking
- Maintenance
- Repairs

# **EDUCATION**

#### IT ENGINEERING

Universidad de Guadalajara

**=** 08/2019 - 06/2023

# **SKILLS**

#### Python Development

**Desktop applications Data Analysis Data Visualization Machine Learning** 

WEB Development **Github HTML CSS JavaScript PHP** MySQL **React Native** Networking

**Initial Configuration Trobleshooting Network Addressing** Design

**Adobe Photoshop Filmora** 

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

**Applied Data Science with Python IBM** 

**Data Visualization Using Python** 

**Python for Data Science** 

**Junior Cybersecurity Analyst Career** Cisco

# **LANGUAGES**

German Intermediate **English** Advanced